[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "What color are often the domes of churches in Russia?",
   "Answer": "Gold colored"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "In which Spanish city did the Joan Miro museum open in 1975?",
   "Answer": "Barcelona"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "Which Italian artist painted the Birth of Venus?",
   "Answer": "Botticelli"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "Who was the original author of Dracula?",
   "Answer": "Bram Stoker"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "In which city is the famous Manneken Pis fountain?",
   "Answer": "Brussels"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "Who is the inventor of photography?",
   "Answer": "Daguerre"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "Which artist painted The Scream?",
   "Answer": "Edvard Munch"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "What is the first book of the Old Testament?",
   "Answer": "Genesis"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "Who did the Mona Lisa paint?",
   "Answer": "Leonardo Da Vinci"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "In which English town did Adolf Hitler study art?",
   "Answer": "Liverpool"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "Which famous French engineer designed two bridges for the city of Porto?",
   "Answer": "Gustave Eiffel"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "In which city can you see Michelangelo’s David?",
   "Answer": "Florence"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "What is called the Jewish candlestick with special religious meaning?",
   "Answer": "Menorah"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "What is the Kabbalah?",
   "Answer": "A System of Jewish Mystical Beliefs"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "Who painted the ceiling of the Sistine Chapel?",
   "Answer": "Michelangelo"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "In which country was the famous painter El Greco born?",
   "Answer": "Greece"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "In which city is the composer Frédéric Chopin buried?",
   "Answer": "Paris"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "Who did paint the famous painting Guernica?",
   "Answer": "Picasso"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "In which city did Romeo and Julia live?",
   "Answer": "Verona"
 }
]
